Previously on JoJo's Bizarre Adventure...
Um-ta-da-da!
Here he is!
That sly bastard, Avdol, is still alive!
Isn't that great?
Mr.
Joestar and Jotaro were the
ones who tended to the wounds
on my head back in India after
I was shot by Hull Horse.
But I also had Avdol do some shopping
for me while he was laying low.
That's right!
From here on out, we're
riding to Egypt in this!
You...
you gotta be kidding!
How did you afford this?!
Sister Dust
Thank you.
The terrain has changed
for Jotaro and company,
who've entered what
divers across the globe?
call the most beautiful sea in the world.
Flanked on the east and west by desert,
the Red Sea was once believed to have
been surrounded by crimson sands.
Today,
its general lack of pollution
and inflowing river water
makes it one of the most immaculate
bodies of water on Earth.
Hang on a minute.
Are you telling me you can
drive this thing, Avdol?
It's not a problem
whatsoever, Polnareff. Wow.
And Avdol's not the only one.
Don't even think about it.
I refuse to let you put
us through another crash.
Well, you sure seem to
be in a foul mood today.
So this is a submarine.
I have to say, I'm a bit surprised.
It's a lot more spacious than I expected.
Isn't it?
Rich folks typically use vessels
like these when they want
to get away for a while and
explore the seafloor for pleasure.
As you can see, it even has windows.
Whoa, c 'est génial!
You know, come to think of it, I've
always sort of liked this kind of thing.
Although I wish I could have
ridden in one with a cute girl.
Once again, you haven't
changed, Polnareff.
Now could you please try just
once to take this seriously?
Hmm? What's that?
This is sonar.
It uses reflective sound waves to detect
underwater objects, much like radar. Wow.
All clear.
I'm not picking up
anything in our vicinity.
With this machine, we can detect
anyone trying to attack us,
no matter which direction the
enemy decides to come from.
But if someone did attack us in here,
There'd be nowhere for us to run.
We'd be like trapped rats.
Don't forget where we are.
60 meters below sea level.
This sub is amazing.
But I guess it is a pleasure
cruiser for the wealthy.
It has a refrigerator,
a coffee maker, and it's even equipped
with the latest in satellite phones.
Hey, Kick! I should call.
Would you mind getting me
a drink while you're up?
I'm dying of thirst here.
I'll take one too. Sure.
Hmm?
Is Cola okay?
Old man, why are you just standing there?
Something bugging you?
Men, I need you to give
me a moment's quiet.
I just remembered I have
a phone call to make.
A phone call? To where?
Where is right.
Who would you need to call from a
submarine in the middle of the Red Sea?
Someone important, I assure you.
You might even call it a delicate matter.
So, as I said, I need you all to be quiet.
Oh, heavens me!
I just don't know!
Which one should I pick?
Between the two, the sparkly
design is much more to my liking.
But is it appropriate for
the charity event tomorrow?
Perhaps a refreshing
white would be better.
What do you think, Roses?
Both of the gowns look
lovely on you, madam.
Coming!
Yes, hello?
Oh, Joseph, darling, it's you!
Where have you been?
And where are you calling from?
What was that, dear?
It's a bit hard to hear you.
Right, sorry.
I'm at a hotel.
Here's the thing.
I hate to say it, but I have to attend
some unexpected business that's come up.
Oh, goodness.
It must be difficult traveling on business
to another country right
after going to Japan.
It's been nearly a month, hasn't it?
Yeah, it has. Sorry.
By the way, Susie, have
you spoken to Holly?
Why, yes, I have.
In fact, I spoke to her
on the phone yesterday.
She mentioned catching a cold that's
developed into a bout of pneumonia.
She tried convincing me
that it wasn't serious,
but I'm thinking about going to visit her.
No, don't.
There's no need for that.
I'm positive she'll recover quickly.
You're such a worried...
So this is what he meant
by a delicate matter?
Indeed.
Madam Joestar is still as
effervescent as someone half her age,
so he checks in now and again to ensure
she doesn't visit Miss Holly in Japan.
That way she's protected from the truth.
Are you saying that she... I am.
She hasn't been told anything.
There's no need to
worry her unnecessarily.
There's nothing to worry about.
Well, if you say so.
All right, I understand.
I'll hold off on going to Japan.
While I have you on the line,
there's something I need to ask you.
I'm having a hard time deciding whether I
should wear the white
dress or the purple one.
Is that so?
Susie, I need to speak to Roses.
Could you pass the phone to him?
What?
Madam, have you considered wearing
your blue dress to the event?
If I remember correctly, it's
in the back of the closet.
That's right.
I'll go and have a look at it.
Hello, Master Joseph.
It's me, Roses. Where's Susie?
She left the room, sir.
There's no chance of her
overhearing our conversation now.
I see.
I'm actually calling from the submarine
that the two of us spoke of a while back.
That I take it you were successful
in reuniting with Master Avdol?
That's right.
Now then, tell me about Holly's condition.
Surely by now you've gotten hold of the
doctors from the Speedwagon Foundation.
Well, actually, when speaking
to her mother on the phone,
Miss Holly says that her illness
is nothing more than a cold.
She's quite insistent that
there's no cause for alarm,
but her condition worsens by the day.
Master Joseph,
don't you think the time has finally
come to tell Madame Joestar the truth?
No.
There's no need to get her riled up.
We're going to put an end
to all this very soon.
I want Holly to go back to her normal
life and never know about any of this.
Don't inform my wife of what's going on.
Under any circumstances.
I'll call again soon.
If that is what you wish, sir?
I pray for your safe return.
Oh, no?
Did you hang up the phone already?
I wasn't finished talking to him yet.
Oh, madam!
It's no matter.
Why don't we have some tea?
You will join me for a cup, won't you?
Madam Oh please madam Allow me to
serve the tea for you Are you sure?
I'm sorry you have to do that. Truly.
But you can rest easy, because
we're right here behind you.
We'll be in Egypt before you know it.
We must defeat Dio as soon as we can,
and save Miss Holly from his curse.
I have returned from the
brink, for this very reason.
Thanks, you guys. Really.
Ah, driving this is actually pretty easy.
I suppose that's how you were
making it look so simple, Avdol.
For Pete's sake.
Hey, don't get so carried away.
Believe it or not, the sea has
its fair share of rough terrain.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
All right, let's speed
this tub up a little bit.
Goldoraf, what are you doing?
It has nothing to do with that.
You gotta believe me.
Eww, I'm so tired.
Tell me when we're almost there.
Hmm.
One, two, three, four, five.
Oh, there's exactly five cups in here.
Hey!
Hurry up and make the coffee, man.
I want some now.
Why don't you make it yourself?
Good news!
I've just spotted the coast of Africa.
We'll be there soon.
Seawater has worn away
the rocks and carved
out an underwater tunnel
near this coral reef.
The exit is 200 meters inland, which makes
this the perfect spot for us to surface.
At long last, we finally
made it. Wolf, huh?
It took long enough.
So this is Egypt.
It is.
We have arrived.
Hmm, what's so funny nothing?
I'm just feeling sort of happy is all It's
been quite a while since the five of us.
We're all gathered together like this
Hey, talk you in why'd you
grab six cups for five people?
That's peculiar.
I guess I didn't notice I
could have sworn it was five
Oh man! Mr. Joestar!
Impossible! It's a stand!
I don't know how, but it
managed to sneak aboard!
It disappeared! No, it didn't!
It transformed!
I'm sure of it.
The stand disguised itself as one of the
gauges, just like with the coffee cup.
Come again? Man!
The coral reef is right there!
And we were only a few hundred
meters from reaching Egypt!
On the bright side, it looks like Mr.
Joestar was only knocked unconscious.
The problem is his hand.
The phone!
Who'd be calling us at a time like this?
Ignore it, Polnareff!
We have to stay focused!
It's the High Priestess!
Careful!
Our enemy's using a deadly
stand called the High Priestess!
So how do we win?
By knowing the user.
The name of this particular
stand user is Rose.
She has the ability to control
her stand from far away,
so she's most likely on land.
What's its power?
It can turn into almost any inanimate
object, as long as it comes from a mineral.
Plastics, metal, glass, or vinyl.
Its transformations are perfect.
There's no way to recognize the
thing until it decides to attack.
That's freaky.
But how did it sneak aboard the
submarine in the first place?
I get it now, so that's how it did it.
How simple.
It cut a hole and moseyed on in.
The stand found a way to
damage the ballast tanks.
We're sinking even faster now.
Not to mention, we're losing oxygen.
We've got to get out of here.
Oh, no!
Shut up!
Who's ever calling us horrible timing?
Jotaro!
Hey, remember anything we
touched might be the...
Hi again, Joseph. It's me.
We weren't finished with the
conversation we were having earlier,
so I made Roses give me your number.
Hmm?
Why aren't you speaking?
And come to think of it, what's
with all the ruckus over there?
Whatever's in the background
sounds like a siren.
I also hear running water.
Is a bathtub overflowing?
I'm sorry, but the old man
can't come to the phone.
I know that voice. Is that you? Jotaro?
Where's Joseph?
You should be in Japan.
Why are you with your grandfather?
Jotaro!
Answer me!
There's nothing to worry
about, Grandma Susie.
He's gonna be just fine,
because I'm right here with him.
Later.
We'll call back once
things calm down. Jotaro!
Oh, uh...
Brace yourselves, people!
We're about to hit the bottom!
Oh, my God!
I knew this would happen to us somehow!
It's like every vehicle we ride
in ends up getting destroyed!
That is the last straw.
I'm never riding in a submarine again.
How strange.
I was getting through a moment ago.
But now it seems as though
the line's suddenly gone dead?
And why was Jotaro there?
Hey, you guys, the air is
getting pretty thin in here.
Kakyoin, I need your help.
Did you catch which one of the
gauges the stand merged with?
Well, from what I can tell, it
looked like it turned into this one.
That's not it!
Jotaro, it's already moved!
It's right behind Kakuin!
Hierophant Green!
Kakuin!
Everyone, head for the door, quickly!
The stand's become part of the whole surface
and is traveling through the machines!
Yeah, you say that, but...
If we stay in this room any longer,
there's a very good chance that none
of us will leave with our lives.
Kakyoin, are you alright?
Yes, I'm fine.
Come on, everyone, to the next room!
We'll seal the room
off and trap it inside!
There's no way it already moved to the
door and transformed itself into the wheels
I have to let go before it's too late
its claws were able to slice through mr.
Joestar's prosthetic
hand like it was nothing
what oh
yeah we got
it that was Of course.
Apparently, our little friend here
isn't as fast as Star Platinum.
So, what should we do with it?
Show no mercy, Jotaro. Don't hesitate.
Here's an idea.
Why don't we begin by
ripping off his little head?
Works for me.
That bastard.
I transformed into a freaking razor.
How are we gonna beat it?
It's strong! Damn!
I can't believe it outsmarted Johtaro.
What an enemy.
Huh?
What the hell is going on?
Whatever's happening here, I'm
pretty sure that we're in a pinch.
Shut up, old man.
That beast will attack us if we touch it,
which means we should
use our stands instead.
Magicians, run!
Hilda Chariot!
That Stan's a tough one!
Chariot's rapier can't pierce its armor!
Come on, pick up the pace!
We've got to attack before it gets away!
I need all of you to stand back!
There's still some oxygen over here!
But it's going to run out before long!
Are you alright, sir?
Yeah!
Forget it, Jojaro!
It'll only transform again!
We're taking on water fast, so we
need to find a way to trap that thing.
We'll figure out how to fight it then.
Don't get too cocky because
this battle isn't over.
I'll kick your ass soon enough.
What'd you say?
Jotaro, why in the hell would you
answer a phone call from Susie? Damn it!
You know you really
shouldn't have done that.
Whatever.
We'll talk about it when
we get out of this mess.
Leave everything to me.
Yeah?
Do you have a plan? You bet.
And it's a brilliant one.
The one and only Joseph Joestar
has been in more situations like
this that he can count on the
prosthetic hand he left behind.
For the life of me, I can't begin to
understand why Jotaro is with Joseph.
Has Joseph said anything? No, ma 'am.
Although, my heart jumped with joy to
hear that boy's voice after so long.
I've heard my precious little grandson
has been quite the handful as of late?
But deep down, he's a sweet child
who cares very much for his family.
Whatever they're doing, I'm sure he's
helping Joseph as much as he can.
You have no idea how right you are, madam.
Master Jotaro and Master
Joseph are most likely in
the midst of battling a
common enemy as we speak.
They're fighting tooth and
nail to save Miss Holly,
someone very dear to them,
from a curse of unbridled evil.
What do we do now?
I have a feeling that she-devil of a stand
isn't really the one who's
actually trapped here.
Sooner or later,
that monster's going to cut its way
out of that room and catch up to us.
And to make matters even worse,
as long as we're surrounded by all
this machinery, we're sitting ducks.
The submarine is done for anyway.
We need to abandon ship and escape.
We'll just have to find some
other way to make it to Egypt.
Are you forgetting that we're
40 meters below sea level?
I know it doesn't sound that far down, but
how are we supposed to get out of here?
Are we really scuba
diving all the way there?
In my entire life, I've never
done anything like this.
Hurry, everyone!
Suit up on the devil!
Ah, good grief. Ah,
I just realized there's
no way I'll be able
to suit up in time with this busted hand.
Can you help me out, Jotaro?
Do it yourself.
Oh my
god...
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick.
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They've got the money on a bed.
Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Foreign types with a hookah. I say.
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop, you drink.
Then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings, oh, hey-oh.
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say,
Walk like an Egyptian.
You must never panic, no matter what.
Just look at how
beautiful it is down here.
will use this to say okay.
But when they aren't, use this.
I would have liked to have seen
your face if only this once.